bootic.com 2014-06-29

# Privacy Policy | Bootic, The Ecommerce Network

This Privacy Policy will govern your use of the Bootic.com website as well as any of its related Services ("Bootic.com", "Site", "Services", "us", "we", "ours") which is provided by Bootic, Inc. and Bootic.com which provides an online environment that enables you to buy and sell products online. 

### What this Privacy Policy Covers

In America we understand that privacy matters that's why we have changing rooms and private stalls in public restrooms. And at Bootic.com we understand that your privacy matters, this is why we provide this transparent, plain English, easy to read Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy only applies to our Site and the Bootic.com Service. Some of the third parties that utilize our Service may also use, collect, and share information for many purposes on their sites and we are not responsible for any of the information that may be collected or used by them. 

Your use of Bootic.com, such as access to data and use of the Services, is governed by this Privacy Policy. At Bootic.com we're happy that the prohibition amendment passed in 1933. In that spirit, this Privacy Policy may be amended from time to time by us, and your continued use of the Site and Services is consideration for having read and agreed to this. If you do not agree with any of the terms of this agreement you must immediately terminate your participation and notify us of your intentions so that we can take appropriate action to delete any data. By using, visiting, registering, or interacting, or continuing to use this Site you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

You must be at least 18 years of age or older to use the Bootic.com Site and Service. If you are under the age of 18, please do not attempt to register for the Site or Service or provide any personal information to us and cease using this site immediately. 

## SUMMARY OF KEY PRINCIPLES

This is a brief summary of what you will be reading in this Privacy Policy: 

  * There are two classes of information that we collect: (a) information about those who use our Site; and (b) the information collected through the Bootic.com Service used to provide its Services to you (c) hmmm were you paying attention? We just said only two;
  * his information is transmitted to, held and processed by our servers which may not be in the same state or country or planet that you are in, so you consent to this transfer;
  * We typically use this information to provide you with information about us, to deliver our Services, and to produce reports and data related to our Service.

## Information that we collect and How it is Used

  * ### Information that you provide to us and how we use it - "Personal Information"

By registering for the Bootic.com's site and Service you may be providing personal information to us. This information may include, but is not limited to, your name, e-mail address, mailing address, telephone number, credit card information, astrology sign, favorite food, company name, and other information required to deliver our services. Your use may also allow you to provide us with information as you interact with the Site. 

In addition to the above, we also collect non-personal information, such as information about your browser, referring URL, cookies, IP address, ISP, operating system, and other information. 

We use third parties to collect, store, and analyze information at some time in the future at our discretion, for the purpose of website analytics relating to conversions, marketing, searches, and other information of interest to us. In the future we hope to use this information to build a fully functioning robot of you. In all seriousness, we collect this information to learn how to better serve you the User. 

We may use your information to send you e-mails and respond to inquiries, send birthday notices, as well as enhance or improve the user experience, our website, and service. 

  * ### COOKIES - baked and soft

We all love cookies my personal favorite is snickerdoodle, is that an overshare? At Bootic.com we use cookies in order to track sessions and to authenticate you—this is necessary to help us distinguish you from other users and to fill your shopping cart. For this reason, you must have cookies enabled in your web browser in order to access and use our website or service. 

  * ### Information Collected by our ISP

We may employ third party companies and individuals to help us manage our servers, databases, and analytics. These third parties may have access to your information only to perform those tasks, and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. The hosting provider for this Site has the ability to record various pieces of information, including domain name, pages accessed, date and time of access, web browser type and computer operating system, and referring information. This information is stored in our server log and may be accessible to us from time to time. 

  * ### Release of Information for Legal Reasons.

The 5-0 or the po po fo sho. If we are contacted by law enforcement we may release your information. Also, we may release information when we believe it is necessary or appropriate to comply with the law (for example, pursuant to a statutory demand, subpoena, warrant or court order), to protect against fraudulent, abusive or unlawful use of the Site or Service, to protect our rights or property, enforce any contract between you and us, or if we reasonably believe that a situation involving danger of death or injury to any person requires disclosure. 

  * ### Transfer of information.

We reserve the right to transfer your information in the event of a change in entity structure, or acquisition of substantial portion of the assets of our company or its parent company. In such event, we will notify you when the information is transferred and the privacy policy changes. 

## How you can change or remove information

  * ### Accessing and Editing your Information

Like He-man you have the power. Users may in some cases be able to review and edit the personal information they have provided to us by logging into your account on the Site and editing your account. Although most changes may occur immediately, information may still be stored in a web browser's cache. We take no responsibility for stored information in your cache, or in other devices that may store information, and disclaim all liability of such. In addition, we may, from time to time, retain residual information about you in our backup and/or database. 

## Other Term

  * ### Commercial and Non-Commercial E-mail Communications

By providing information to the Site that forms the basis of communication with you, such as contact information, you waive all rights to file complaints concerning unsolicited email from this website since, by providing such information, you agree to receive communication from us. However, you may unsubscribe from certain communications via the website or by notifying the Site that you no longer wish to receive solicitations or information and we will endeavor to remove you from the database. When unsubscribing to our e-mails please don't write "!*&#&^*&!@" or send a picture of a LOLcat, just be nice and send us a simple "unsubscribe". 

Specifically, we may use your information to send e-mails about our site our respond to inquiries; send news about products, news, or updates related to Bootic.com. 

  * ### Limited Use

Although we do not intend to sell, share, or rent information obtained on the Site other than as discussed in this privacy policy we reserve the right to do so in the future. If we do, we will update this Privacy Policy to reflect those definitive changes. 

  * ### Data Security and Risks inherent with information sharing

We all know that the Internets are an unreasonable place, seriously, have you seen the threads on Reddit? But Bootic.com takes reasonable measures to protect the security of your personal information, your usage of the Service, and your usage of the Site. We take reasonable precautions to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. However, you understand and agree that the purpose of the Site is to facilitate the exchange of information with us and other third parties, and, as a consideration for viewing, communicating with, or using the Site in any manner, including placing Bootic.com links on your site, you waive all claims of any nature against us and our owners, directors, officers, employees, agents and representatives concerning the loss, alteration, or misuse of information. 

In essence, what we're trying to say is that no security measures are perfect. There is no guarantee that any information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by any breach of any physical, technical, or other safeguards. Additionally, we cannot guarantee that robotic sharks with lasers won't take over the world. Nor can we guarantee that any information that you share on the Site or with other users will not become publicly available. You assume all responsibility and liability for, and agree to hold us and our owners, directors, officers, employees, agents and representatives harmless for the use or misuse your personal data, including the use of such data by others that use such information in an inappropriate way or that may cause you harm. 

  * ### Changes in This Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we may post those changes on the Site so you can remain aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Your continued use of Bootic.com.com is consideration for your acceptance of any changes to the Privacy Policy. 

  * ### Minors

We love the kids... however, individuals under 18 years of age are not allowed to use our Site or Service. If you are under the legal age of 18 years old do not apply for or submit any personal information to this Site or our Service. 

  * ### Advertiser and Third Party Websites

Please be aware that this Privacy Policy, and any other policies in place, in addition to any amendments, does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to members of the Service or Site. Bootic.com.com bears no responsibility for the information collected or used by any advertiser or third party website. Please review the privacy policy and terms of service for each site you visit through third party links. 

  * ### International Transfer

Although we have no intention of moving to Canadia aka America Junior. Your information may be transferred to - and maintained on - computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, Bootic.com transfers Personal Information to the United States and processes it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer. 

## NOTE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS (ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT OF 2003 - OPPA)

Bootic.com is located in the State of California, because we love the weather and wine! We also permit residents of California to use its services. Therefore, it is the intent of the Bootic.com to comply with the California Business and Professions Code §§ 22575-22579. If you are a California resident you may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to any third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Various provisions throughout this Privacy Policy address requirements of the Californian privacy statutes. In summary, you must presume that we collect electronic information from all visitors. You may contact us at with at [info@bootic.com](mailto:info@bootic.com) with any privacy questions. 

**NOTE:** This Privacy Policy was lasted updated on May 17, 2012. This privacy policy applies to the Site and any subdomains of the Site. This privacy policy does not apply to any third party website as their content is not controlled by us. Please contact the administrator of any other site for information about their own privacy policies and the information they collect about their site visitors.
